(Leonard:)Okay.
If you need to pause
a little longer,
just click the pause button.
But the show must go on.
And thankfully, all the things
my girlfriend used to do
can be taken care of
with my right hand.
Anyway, let's not spend
any more time talking about her.
We're here to talk about flags.
Tonight's theme:
flags of countries
that have been torn apart
and the women I have a feeling
were responsible.
(Leonard:)You guys have any idea
how much it costs
(Leonard:)to see a marriage
counselor?
$250 an hour. Why?
(Raj:)How do you know?
(Howard:)Bernadette and I have
occasionally gone to one to,
(Howard:)you know, stay on top of things.
(Raj:)And I'm just
hearing about this now?
(Howard:)Dude, just because
we're best friends
(Howard:)doesn't mean that I have to tell
you everything that goes on.